[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: Characters, locations, and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only; viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
I should be happy because I'm done with Mr. Sarm.
But why is it the opposite?
It's okay if our love got cut short.
At least my priority was making good memories together,
even if you didn't choose me.
We're all grownups now.
Don't complicate things.
If you miss him,
just go see him.
It's as simple as that.
If I miss him...
I should go see him?
Ow...
Little Jam.
Mr. Sarm?!
- Let me go! - What are you doing?
You can't.
I haven't done anything wrong!
I repeat!
I love you!
I love you every single second!
I love you with every breath I take!
Listen...
I love you.
What should we do with him?
Take him away, Poj.
Huh?!
Come with us.
- Huh? - Now!
♫I've held back, but you're impossible to resist♫
♫'Cause you make me wanna kiss, kiss♫
♫Never thought I'd fall for you♫
♫Accidentally gave you my heart♫
♫Wanna be close to you, can you tell me if this is love?♫
♫It feels so right, should I let my heart take control?♫
♫You're too cute, you drive me crazy♫
♫Just a glance from you almost melts me, baby♫
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou, ou♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫Everyone tells me to hold my horses♫
♫But the sight of you bugs my system♫
♫You in my heart, I won't miss my chance♫
♫Aiming right at you, only you♫
♫Six, five, four, three, two, one♫
♫I'll count it down♫
♫One more sec, and I'll kiss, kiss you, alright♫
♫Wanna be close to you, can you tell me if this is love?♫
♫You in my heart, I won't miss my chance♫
♫You're too cute, you drive me crazy♫
♫Just a glance from you almost melts me, baby♫
[Your Third Series]
Juju.
Where are you running off to?
Hey.
Oh?
Good morning...sir.
Oh...
You were the guy who came here last night.
Good morning.
I've come in peace today.
I've got you a gift.
I run an orange farm, you see.
That's why I've got you a voucher.
You can redeem it for any product,
with no quantity limit,
all year long.
And here...
A free vacation.
Accommodation is available at the nature campground
on my farm.
Whoa...
Is this from Adisuan Farm?
My wife and kids have been wanting to visit the campground for years now,
but it's always fully booked.
It fills up so quickly.
Take them. For you,
I can give it my all.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
Do you have an ulterior motive here?
Sir.
How could you ask me such a question?
I just want us to get along well
because
I'll be a resident here.
Oh?
You're going to purchase a house here?
Indeed.
Uh, sir.
Excuse me.
Which one is Mr. Jiranat's house?
All of them, actually.
Mr. Jiranat owns this residential project.
This is nothing fancy.
I'm just buying a house from my soon-to-be partner's residential project.
I haven't introduced myself, actually.
I'm...
Sarm Traiphop.
Right.
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
I'm Poj, a security guard.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm off to see Mr. Jam now.
Today, I'm doing things properly.
Don't worry.
- Right. - Alright.
- Go ahead. - Right.
Little Jam.
Little Jam...
Little Jam!
Is he alright?
Little Jam...
Is he fine?
Need to change into flip-flops,
or else I'll get scolded.
The door isn't locked either.
Why is he so careless about security?
Mr. Sarm?
How did you come in?
Little Jam.
I'm sorry.
I just let myself in
because this door
wasn't locked.
That wasn't my intention.
Actually,
I texted you earlier,
but you didn't reply.
I called you...
but you didn't answer.
So I got worried,
thinking that something happened to you.
So I trespassed.
I'm sorry.
I was probably zoning out.
Little Jam.
Are you sick?
Oh...
I'm feeling better now.
I already took my medications.
Have you eaten?
Why are you like this?
If that's the case...
allow me to use the kitchen.
Right.
I didn't order anything.
I did.
Boiled crabs,
your favorite.
Where are the crabs?
Here.
I am not in the mood.
Fine...
Let me use the kitchen, then.
Are you hungry?
A little.
Have a hot bowl of soup.
It'll help you get better quicker.
Thank you.
Once it cools down, put it in the fridge.
You can reheat it for tomorrow.
Thank you.
Can you change that word to something else?
To what?
Can I stay here for one night?
Please?
You rode your motorbike here?
That's...right.
I vroomed, vroomed, vroomed my way here
so I could arrive sooner.
I wanted to see you as soon as possible
because I was worried about you.
By the time he rides back from here...
it'll already be late at night...
He will probably fly down the road rather than just ride along.
Dangerous...
I am worried about him.
Fine.
Oh...
The guest room has recently been repainted.
It still smells like paint.
Oh,
that's nothing, Little Jam.
I can sleep on the couch.
I'm easygoing,
not a picky eater.
I'm also low-maintenance.
I'll do just fine in any scenario.
I can even sleep on the floor.
Right.
Sure.
Yes!
Hm?
Ah.
It's the black pepper.
It stings.
Are you okay?
I am, yes.
I really am.
♫You're my love battery♫
♫I've never been someone's priority♫
♫Always been through heartbreak endlessly♫
Yes!
♫So many have come into my life and left me♫
♫I've got nobody to stay right here beside me♫
♫All alone...♫
♫All alone, I'm restless night and day♫
♫My heart just doesn't feel okay♫
♫Like this, even paracetamol won't make it go away♫
♫But then you came and stirred things up this way♫
♫And my heart began to change♫
♫I just want you to know…♫
♫You're the positive energy in my life whenever I'm tired♫
♫Just having you near...♫
♫You charge my heart and bring me back to life♫
Mr. Sarm.
Yes, Little Jam?
Here,
your towel and clothes.
Use the bathroom downstairs.
As for the worn clothes,
toss them in the rattan basket by the bathroom.
I will dry the laundry.
Okay.
Let me get the bedding for you,
but hang tight
because I need to shower first.
You can't, Little Jam.
Just give yourself a sponge bath.
You're still warm to the touch.
I am taking a warm shower.
Are you sure?
Mm.
Okay.
Okay, sure.
Little Jam.
Here is your pillow and blanket, Mr. Sarm.
Thank you.
Sweet dreams.
Little Jam.
By the way...
Is Juju not here?
No,
Mr. Sib borrowed her for a commercial shoot.
Whoa...
A celebrity cat.
Did he pay you for this?
He did not.
He didn't?
He did not hold back.
With this...
do you miss your cat?
Of course, I do.
It is not like we have never been apart before.
I was away for months when I was in Pak Chong.
Meow.
I'll be your cat, then.
My cat is only this tiny.
Just like you.
You're this tiny...
But here...
So chubby.
I am going to bed now.
Little Jam.
Aren't we going to clear things up about what happened that day?
Has it been seven days already?
Why seven days?
You said you would be mad at me for a week.
I'm sorry...
for turning away from you
on that day.
Well, you were upset.
It was on me, too,
for hiding the truth from you.
I owe you an apology myself.
No.
No, Jam.
It wasn't your fault.
It was my fault
for not listening to you.
No,
it was my fault.
You asked me what I was doing,
but I chose to double down.
No, Little Jam.
You're not to blame here.
It's me.
You were simply following Sib's order.
I get it.
It's on me.
No...
If that's the case,
how about we share the blame between us?
Mm, mm.
Sure thing.
By the way,
are you not mad at me anymore?
I never actually get mad at you.
Forget being mad at you for seven days, seven months, or whatever.
It is already killing me
to be mad at you for seven hours.
I thought...
I would never get to see you again.
Little Jam...
what made you think that?
You mean business when you get angry.
You gave me a scary look, too.
When we were on Ko Pha-ngan,
I told you that
I'd come see you when it was over,
didn't I?
On top of that...
didn't I already tell you after the New Year's party...
that I love you?
"I love you, Little Jam."
Mr. Sarm?!
Are you okay, Mr. Sarm?
Was that you confessing your love without actually saying "love"?
Mr. Sarm!
Mr. Sarm, are you...
It's okay if you can't say it right now.
I'm right here,
and I won't go anywhere.
"I love you, Little Jam."
Mr. Sarm!
Kindly adore this cat,
too.
If you like cats,
then I'll be one.
My cat has to get smooched.
That is how I always smooch Juju.
Get plenty of rest if you're sick, alright?
Go to bed already.
"I love you, Little Jam."
Good night.
Are you okay, Mr. Sarm?
I am.
I really am.
I'm fine, really.
I am hitting the hay, then.
Bye-bye.
Good night.
Bye-bye...
"I love you, Little Jam."
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss? (Ohhhh, oh)♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss? (Just you, only you, can it be you?)♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more (Hoo, woo)♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie (Hoo, woo)♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou (If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind)♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou, ou (If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind)♫
[One day later]
[Two days later]
Mr. Sarm...
What is it?
I came to tell you that I'm leaving.
Let me send you off downstairs.
It's okay.
Go back to bed.
I came here to tell you that
I made you xiaolongbao in the kitchen.
Reheat it, and it's good to go.
I've also made you fresh orange juice.
Drink it while you're at the office
so you'll feel refreshed.
I sliced up a dragon fruit for you, too.
It's in the fridge.
The container is...
light blue.
You're so sweet.
Then love me already.
I'll be going now.
Mm...
Stay safe on the road.
Do not go too fast,
- understand? - Got it.
I have to go now.
Maybe not.
- Just kidding. - I'll go now.
You should get going now.
I'm going now, alright?
I'm leaving, okay?
You heard that, right?
I'm leaving now, okay?
Alright.
I'm going for real now, okay?
I'll be going now.
- I'm going now, okay? - Mm.
Have a safe trip.
I'm going now.
Get going already.
Bye-bye.
This necklace...
I once told Little Jam to never take it off.
Yet he did.
Soon...
there's something I want to give him.
I hope he'll forever keep it on.
Right.
Say the line.
Right now?
Mm.
Right now.
Are you waiting for a ribbon-cutting ceremony?
Do you need me to call someone?
Okay, okay.
Here I go, okay?
Yeah, please.
Any minute now.
Shall we begin?
Come on!
Don't rush me.
Haven't you felt nervous before?
Yes, I have,
but it's been four hours already, Sarm.
Are you going to marry him or what?
Of course, I am.
Just give me a second.
No marriage, then, I suppose.
Watch your mouth!
How about this, Sarm?
I think...
you should try...
relaxing
and just say...
what's on your mind.
Where do I even start?
I think...
You can start with
when you two first met.
When I first met him,
I pulled him by the shirt just like this.
Then I thought
that tiny guy was so chatty, annoying,
and obnoxious.
Is that it?
Mm...
I think...
you need some rest, Sarm.
Just...
stay relaxed.
I'll get you a drink.
By the way...
do you want gotu kola tea...
or a drink of disappointment?
Oh, damn you!
Go there.
Sit over there.
Gosh.
Sit down!
Here.
Orange juice again?!
Why can't I ever escape oranges in this life?
I want to go ask Dad,
"Why the orange farm?!"
Can we have a grapefruit farm instead?
Gosh...
But Little Jam loves oranges.
Little Jam loves orange jam.
Mm.
Okay.
The orange farm can stay, then.
Thanks.
Drink up.
Refreshing!
Mm.
Good, good, good.
Now, then...
Now that you're refreshed, shall we...
try again? Okay?
Now, try...
talking about
your first impression.
Think about it.
Do you have any?
Yeah.
Tell me about it.
Mm.
Gosh.
Listen.
I'm
very impressed by him.
He's talented,
smart,
a fast learner,
a runner,
- Right... - a hearty eater,
and a debater.
Oh,
he also crashes out a lot.
He's just so damn cute.
He's my jam.
Gosh, Sarm...
If I were Jam,
I would've rejected you.
You're as stiff as a rock.
Try again.
You've got this.
♫I want to be called your lover♫
♫I want your arm entwined with mine♫
♫Like what lovers do♫
That... That was decent.
Try to keep it going.
Here's the deal.
We might have started
on the wrong foot,
but
my feelings have changed.
Right now,
I can't live without you.
Yeah.
If I don't get to see you,
I'll probably miss you to death.
Everyone knows,
as do the ghosts
and the spirits at the orange farm,
that...
I'm a few cards short of a full deck.
Mm.
It's dead obvious.
But you...
make me
complete.
Wow...
Now, my life
can't go on without you.
Why is that, you may ask?
Because you're everything to me.
I...
I love you.
I love you very much
with all the heart one person
can possibly give.
From now on,
I want you to be the first person I wake up to
and the last before going to bed.
I want to see you every day
because you're the very breath I breathe.
After all of that,
you can probably guess
what I'll say next, can't you?
That's right.
The next thing I want to say is that...
the secret to making tasty boiled crabs
is to add Himalayan salt.
You've got it, Sarm.
Mm.
Perfect!
I think it'll work.
Trust me.
It's good.
Isn't it?
Mm.
Gosh...
I'm a goddamn genius.
But I think you can do more.
With the quote "I love you very much,"
make it sound
much longer.
It'll make it even better.
Really?
Of course.
Won't it sound over the top?
I don't think so.
It'll sound more natural,
for someone like you, that is.
Are you taking a shot at me?
No, you're imagining it.
Gosh.
♫You're my love battery♫
♫I've never been someone's priority♫
♫Always been through heartbreak endlessly♫
"I love you, Little Jam."
Smooch.
This heart is yours.
♫Filling this heart that once felt empty inside♫
♫The positive vibe in my life whenever I'm tired♫
♫Just having you near…♫
Where are you taking me to?
Today,
I'll take you scuba diving to see the beautiful coral
and sea anemones.
Then, we'll have a wonderful lunch.
Mind you, the restaurant has amazing reviews.
Then, we'll take a nap...
recharging ourselves a bit.
Uh...
Once the sun goes down a bit, we'll hike in the woods
and watch a breathtaking sunset!
But right now,
let's get something to eat.
An army marches on its stomach.
And...
What about the banana boat and parasailing?
I want to try them both.
How about tomorrow?
Not today?
How about changing the afternoon nap
to parasailing instead?
Not a great idea, Jam.
It goes against my plan.
What plan?
Well...
Well, the hiking.
Hm...
Uh...
But
I'll take you for extreme activities all over the island tomorrow.
You can do everything you want.
Okay?
Are you sure?
Mm.
Mm,
alright, then.
That's so sweet of you.
Let's have a meal, then.
I don't want to have a meal now.
I want to have you.
It's like what they say,
jam goes well with anything.
Hey!
We are having a meal, right?
Let's go.
Where are you taking me to?
Hey! Stop.
Stop...
Stop it!
Here, Little Jam.
Thank you.
Come here.
Here.
Slowly, okay?
- Be careful. - Right.
Right here.
Here we are.
- Right... - Yay.
Be careful, alright?
If something happens to you,
my heart will break.
See that over there?
Isn't it beautiful?
That island over there?
Yes.
Hey...
Mr. Sarm.
Hm?
I looked so goofy.
How so, Little Jam?
Take a look.
- In every way. - See?
You look really adorable, Little Jam.
I'll
make a print that covers the whole wall,
and I'll display it behind the bed
so I get to see your face every day.
I'm serious.
Thinking about it already makes me happy.
Ridiculous.
Here.
Let me take photos of you instead.
Oh, okay.
Alright, alright.
Let me pose real quick.
Alright.
Make sure you look handsome, okay?
I already am.
Three,
two,
one.
How is it?
Am I handsome enough to be the man of your heart?
Mm...
I think the likes of you
work better as the bad guy against my heart.
Oh, Little Jam.
If I were a bad guy,
I'd be the one...
who loves you deeply,
from the very bottom of my heart.
The very bottom of your heart?
Yes.
Now, now, let's take more selfies.
Three,
two,
one.
Hm.
My cheek will get bruised at this point.
Ha, ha.
It won't get bruised that easily.
Mm...
Oh...
Shooting from every angle.
Are you a vacuum cleaner or what?
Yes...
Oh, Little Jam!
Dolphins!
- Whoa! - Mm.
Shooting in 360 degrees.
We'll get shots from every angle.
Ha, ha.
You teased me again.
What?!
Little Jam,
what's that box?
A box?
Over there. Right there.
Maybe there's something in it.
Maybe it's a treasure.
Go pick it up.
Come on, Little Jam.
I would rather not.
It's okay.
If that's the case, I'll...
I'll... I'll...
Let us not, Mr. Sarm.
In movies, they say...
we should not touch someone else's stuff without permission.
Come on, it's okay.
You would be in trouble if the owner came back and looked for it.
Maybe it's not...
There are no shamans here either.
Little Jam, there's nobody here, though.
Take a peek inside the box...
Exactly.
There is nobody here.
And your feng shui master
is back in Pak Chong.
He cannot save you in time.
Just open it for a second.
It's okay, we'll...
No!
Let us not.
But...
Just a quick peek.
No, stop it, Mr. Sarm!
Try...
If you open it,
we will break up.
But, Little Jam...
Not even a quick peek?
But...
Oh...
You're right, Little Jam.
Who knows what's inside that box.
If there's something dangerous inside,
- nobody can save us, right? - Yes.
Let's leave it there.
Also, it is getting dark.
Mm.
Let us head back, shall we?
Yeah, there are swarms of mosquitoes, too.
Let's get going, then.
- Let us. - Mm.
Little Jam...
I got you a surprise.
Gosh...
I even styled my hair to look this cool.
There goes my plan.
Little Jam.
Mr. Sarm!
Hurry up, Mr. Sarm!
Okay, Little Jam.
Wait for me.
I'm on my way.
Hey.
Get out of there already, Mr. Sarm...
Mr. Sarm!
Yes?
Let us get going.
Quickly, Mr. Sarm!
It is getting dark.
Okay, okay.
I'm coming.
Little Jam...
[Uncle Mai's Kitchen]
Little Jam,
look.
I have dinner prepared for us.
It looks so delicious.
Are you hungry?
You are, aren't you?
Let's have dinner, then.
Come on.
Wow...
Ta-da, ta-da...
Dun-dun, ta-da, ta-da
Da-da
I have to leave early tomorrow.
I cannot stay any longer.
Mr. Sib's client flew here from Hong Kong with his family,
and he wants me to host them.
But...
Isn't tomorrow your day off, Little Jam?
We also have plans.
Oh, right.
Sib has many secretaries.
Can't he let one of them handle the job?
I already hosted the client's family,
so I knew
what he liked
and what his wife and kids were allergic to.
And...
Can't you stay, Little Jam?
Do you see these raindrops?
They...
They're my teardrops.
Mr. Sarm...
I cannot say no to Mr. Sib.
Can I come with you, then?
Please?
Can I come with you?
That is not possible.
Can you not leave, Little Jam?
It's really hard to find time
for a trip together.
You can stay here and enjoy the vacation.
Without you here,
this place means nothing.
I'm not staying.
It's tomorrow no matter what, right?
Mm.
Oh, oh.
Mr. Sarm...
If my life were a soap opera,
it'd be called
"Traiphop's Tears."
The antagonist
would be none other
than my own older brother.
He assigned the task at such perfect timing.
You returned earlier than expected.
Can you prepare gotu kola tea for me?
Make me a full pot.
I'll come back here to enjoy it.
No problem.
Right. Jab and use your hips.
Try jabbing.
Good.
That's good.
Not like that.
Oh?
Mr. Sarm,
did you change your mind and come back to welcome our new boxers?
Not exactly.
How many boxers are in this batch?
Two, actually.
But don't worry,
we've got both an amateur and a professional.
They're all talented.
They're not hard to train.
By the way, Mr. Sarm,
aren't you going to give them a welcome match?
Let them shine on their own.
You've got a great body,
and everyone in Pak Chong knows that
you're the real deal.
Fine.
I'll hop in.
See you soon.
[My Little Jam]
A smartphone can be charged,
but look at me.
Nobody's charging my heart.
Gosh...
[I arrived safe and sound
Do not worry; I will be busy working
Might not get to answer your calls]
[My Little Jam]
[Sarm: Hey]
[Sarm: Still occupied? What are you doing? Have you eaten yet?]
[Sarm: I'm home, actually; I left soon after you did
Being there alone felt too empty]
[Sarm: I had fun boxing today; I got destroyed by a pro
It all hurts, but it's not as bad as not seeing you, Little Jam]
[Sarm: Take care of yourself over there, eat lots of good food,
get plenty of rest, and don't overwork; I'm worried about you]
Whoa!
You're looking at me?
You look at me every day, huh?
Look at the wall instead.
You seem troubled,
as if you've had a fight with your partner.
Mr. Sib...
You are not the real Mr. Sib.
Give me back my real boss.
I'll ask you again.
What's troubling your mind?
If Mr. Sarm disappeared again,
what would you do?
It's simple, really.
I'll send you to find him again,
but this time,
if you can't find him,
do not come back.
Even if you have to turn the whole world upside down,
you have to find him.
I have probably used up all my luck.
Oh?
Why is that?
What did you do to my brother again?
Sarm...
He's my precious little brother.
I have not done anything,
but I do not understand
why he looked that upset either.
I just talked to my dad,
and he said Sarm had just gotten back from Ko Pha-ngan
and looked sad.
He has returned?
Mm.
Oh...
You went there with him, right?
I'm so sorry
for asking you to come here.
I interrupted your time together on your trip, right?
No, not at all.
Uh,
I was just on vacation.
Here's the deal.
How about I teach you
how to stop saying one thing and meaning another?
How much is this training?
If it is affordable, then I will sign up.
You're good at dodging the subject.
At any rate,
if something is troubling you,
don't hold it for too long.
Don't complicate things.
I know you're talented,
and you already know
what you should do.
If I delayed things any longer,
Mr. Sarm might lose himself.
He might not just take a trip to an island
but to outer space.
Mr. Sib.
May I go and follow my heart?
Go ahead.
I always support you.
Also...
follow it through.
Once you reach your destination,
do come back and tell me about it.
Thank you, Mr. Sib!
May your success shine
brighter than fireworks.
Get going already
before it's too late.
Right, Mr. Sib.
I will be on my way, then.
Song.
Jam.
Take a seat.
Thank you.
What brings you here?
Why are you in such a rush?
I need help.
Sarm is mad at me,
and I am here to make it up to him.
Sarm is mad at you, really?
And...
How was the trip to Ko Pha-ngan?
Can you tell me about it?
An urgent task came up, so I had to leave early.
Mr. Sarm seemed a little upset, too.
He did not pick up the phone
or reply to my texts.
And... did...
Did Sarm...
Did he give you the ring?
The ring?
The ring.
What ring?
Well...
When...
someone...
gives another person a ring,
what...does that mean?
They want them to sell it?
No, no.
Jam...
Picture this.
If
someone
wants to give you a ring,
what's their intention?
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
To marry me?
Excellent, Jam!
The intention is to marry.
Now, then,
Sarm
wants to give you
his ring...
This means that he wants to...
He wants to marry me?
Well done!
You hit the nail on the head, Jam.
But that is not possible.
It is possible, Jam.
Think about it.
Did
Sarm ask you...
to look at a certain box?
What's that box?
A box?
Over there. Right there.
That box...
The one I ignored?
He was probably devastated that...
things didn't go according to plan.
And do you know
where Mr. Sarm is?
He's probably somewhere nearby.
He's probably crying so hard that he could flood Pak Chong right now.
Do not wait around, Jam.
What should I do, Song?
Why don't you propose back to him?
If he asks
what you brought to propose with,
just say,
"This kiss."
Trust me.
Works every time.
Thank you, Mr. Song.
You've got this, Jam.
He loves me!
He loves me not!
Mr. Sarm.
Little...
I am here to make it up to you...
Though I am late...
at least I am here.
Do not stay quiet, Mr. Sarm.
You are giving me bad vibes.
What did I tell you to call me?
Sarm.
Didn't catch that.
"Sarm."
Why are you here?
I am here to apply for a position.
You have to go there.
That's the headquarters.
Why did you come for me?
I can only apply for this position with you.
What position exactly?
It's...
The owner of Adisuan Farm's spouse.
I'm sorry, Little Jam?
Am I daydreaming?
I must be.
Little Jam.
Slap me in the face.
Give me a wake-up slap.
This is impossible.
Little Jam.
Give me a slap. A slap, a slap...
Is this clear enough
that this is not a dream?
I'm almost awake now.
Is this clear enough?
Just a little more...
Is it clear now, Sarm?
Do not be so tense.
I am not.
I did it without knowing.
So...
You're making it up to me...
and you want to be my spouse?
Mm.
Do you accept?
If so...
show me what you've got.
I have none.
I always burn an omelet when I make one.
All I can make is cup noodles.
But I can buy you yogurt drinks.
And...
What do you want as your payment?
Love me and take care of me for the rest of your life.
Do not terminate this contract.
And what will I get in return,
hm?
I will take care of you as best as I can.
I'll give you headaches, you know?
Are you cool with that?
I have gotten used to it by now.
And what about me making a big deal out of everything?
I always do it.
You are my jam.
Oh...
It is true.
What about being this goofy?
Can you handle it?
No matter what you are like...
I will always love you.
So, do you accept me or not?
This position has always been yours.
You have no clue at all,
huh?
Let's get married.
Wait...
Aren't I supposed to say that?
And will you?
I will.
I will. I will.
Today.
Right now.
Right here.
Yes.
Right now.
Little Jam,
hold me, please.
I'm passing out.
Got an inhaler?
I have one.
Aside from the inhaler...
do you have my love in your backpack?
I do not
because...
your love
is right here.
I...
love...
you, Sarm.
Oh, Little Jam.
Stop being too adorable, can you?
I've run out of ways to show my love.
Do you think you are the only one falling in love?
I also love you very much.
But I'm still not your first.
You are neither my first
nor my second.
You are not the last either.
But you're my third.
No promotions
or demotions.
You will stay as my third.
And my third means...
my beloved.
And I love you the most, too.
♫I'll simply be right here, always within reach♫
♫Like a gentle breeze bringing you peace♫
♫I'll stay right here by your side, always♫
I've finally got a spouse!
A change of pace to have fun with you.
If either couple starts fighting,
make them sleep in the stable.
Let's do a warm-up.
How exactly?
♫(My mind keeps running wild)♫
♫Don't make me feel things, things♫
♫The way you get close to me, me♫
♫Can you just tell me how you feel?♫
♫Do you feel this love is real?♫
♫That kiss, kiss♫
♫Was it a coincidence or destiny?♫
♫Was that a genuine kiss,♫
♫Or was it a one-time thing?♫
♫Don't make me feel things, things♫
♫The way you get close to me, me♫
♫Can you just tell me how you feel?♫
♫Do you feel this love is real?♫
♫That kiss, kiss♫
♫Was it a coincidence or destiny?♫
♫Was that a genuine kiss,♫
♫Or was it a one-time thing?♫
♫Sneaking a look from afar, I'm not so sure♫
♫Seems like the target isn't yet aware♫
♫Is this real love,♫
♫Or just something temporary?♫
[Your Third Series]